My name is James.
I have sinned against Prophet T.B. Joshua.
I have sinned against God
and I have sinned against The SCOAN.
It all started years back; then, I was a militant.
About 16 years back, I used to be a militant in Bayelsa State.
As such, I have gone to so many places for charms for protection
with the result that if you shoot me, it will not affect me,
if you cut me, it won't penetrate.
I did all this because of the nature of the job that I was doing.
Later, I went for deliverance in one church.
After the deliverance, the man of God asked me to wait,
that he wanted to see me and talk to me, which I did.
After some time, he asked me if I would work with them.
I accepted; I said there is nothing wrong in working in the house of God.
I did not know that he was asking me to blaspheme against the man of God.
I have never met Prophet T.B. Joshua in my life.
I have never even seen him.
I had never even heard the name before.
So, I accepted the offer as they would pay me a huge amount of money
to testify against Prophet T.B. Joshua in any of their crusades
that Prophet T.B. Joshua is a satanic agent from the kingdom of darkness.
That I am in level 7 and he is in level 5, which I accepted
that he never mentions the name Jesus Christ in his church,
he only mentions 'Emmanuel'.
I danced to their tune because of the money involved.
They took me round many states in Nigeria and outside
to confess against the man of God, which I did.
In every crusade, lots of people gathered to listen.
I normally told them that Prophet T.B. Joshua is a fake prophet,
that he came from the pit of hell and that he is a satanic man.
That he and I are from the same occultic kingdom.
This took me through 2004 when I decided to leave the country.
I travelled out of the country, that I wasn't going to stay in Nigeria anymore.
Getting to where I was, I somehow found myself doing rubbish.
My life was somehow useless.
What I don't like doing was what I saw myself doing.
They went as far as calling me because I dropped my number with them
and also inviting me down to Nigeria for the same purpose.
After some time, my wife told me that I needed to put a Christian channel
in my house so that my son and her could have a future through it.
I never accepted but after some time, I said, "Well, let me do that".
I accepted the proposal of my wife and put the Christian channel in my house.
As time went on, I kept watching it.
Most times, when I came home, I would see her watching it and I would be annoyed.
I would say, "What is the meaning of all this? Please, I want to watch a film.
Put a film on; let me watch it. What is the meaning of all this rubbish?"
One day, I just switched to channel 33 where I saw Emmanuel TV.
I said, "What kind of channel is this?"
It was not quite two seconds when I saw The Synagogue Church.
I said, "Ah!"
I was so much interested; I said, "I must see what is happening".
Not up to 5 minutes, I saw the name Prophet T.B. Joshua and I asked myself,
"Could this be the man that I was blaspheming?
No! I don't think so. I have to listen".
In my life, I used to go to church where I played music, sang and did everything.
But to give my life to Christ,
because of what happened to me in the past, I saw church as a game.
I came to realise through watching Emmanuel TV
that I heard Prophet T.B. Joshua saying, "In the name of Jesus Christ!" times without number.
I said, "Ah, ah, but the people who asked me to confess against him said
that he does not mention the name of Jesus Christ, only 'Emmanuel'.
But I have heard Jesus Christ from his mouth, times without number.
No. I don't think I can remain here.
I must come down to Nigeria and free myself,
so that my family and I can have a bright future".
Man of God, please, I need deliverance.
Before I came here, they called me to come down to Nigeria
that a crusade was going to take place this December.
But I replied that I was not ready.
I think you will be delivered through Emmanuel TV.
For viewers all over the world: Many of you don't believe that through television, you can receive.
Through television is as good as a man of God laying hands on you.
I'm going to do that now to the man that claimed he was in the same cult with T.B. Joshua.
I'm stretching my hand towards the screen
and right now, you will see what will happen, in the name of Jesus.
In the name of Jesus Christ!
Out!
Deliverance In Jesus' Name
In the name of Jesus Christ!
Out!
Deliverance In Jesus' Name
Set Free In Jesus' Name
TT: Mel Flowers 10/03/2019
RV: Pavel Tatyana Zheleznyakov 16/03/2019